A Guide to the Stacy May papers FA442
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Subgroup 1, 1919-1972; 1; 34.94 Cubic Feet 74 legal-sized document boxes, 1 oversized box
  - 1960 Campaign Material (Box 42, Folder 258)
  - 1962 Campaign Material (Box 42, Folder 259)
  - North American Newspaper Alliance - 3 Economic Articles, 1963 (Box 42, Folder 260)
  - Norwegian Nobel Institute Conference on Western Democracies and World Problems, Oslo, June 13-21, 1955 (Box 42, Folder 261)
  - Nuclear Testing, 1961-1962 (Box 43, Folder 262)
  - G. Warren Nutter - Correspondence, 1959-1961 (Box 43, Folder 263)
  - Office for Regional Development - Development Plan for New York State, 1963-1964 (Box 43, Folder 264)
  - "Our Answer to the Economic Challenge of Communism", undated (Box 43, Folder 265)
  - "Outlook for Air Transport to 1965", 1954, 1956 (Box 43, Folder 266)
  - "Outlook for Air Transport to 1965" - Charts, 1954 (Box 43, Folder 267)
  - "Outlook for Air Transport to 1965" - Investment Division Supplementary Report, 1954 (Box 43, Folder 268)
  - Panel II - Budget, 1957-1958 (Box 43, Folder 269)
  - Panel III - Stacy May Notes, 1958, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 270)
  - Roswell B. Perkins - DNA Research, 1961-1964 (Box 44, Folder 271)
    Biographical / Historical
    Although the acronym "DNA" may have stood for Definitive News Analysis, no corroboration has been found in the written record. The staff of DNA were on Rockefeller's personal payroll. There were two main divisions to DNA, a research group for Nelson A. Rockefeller. The Domestic Policy staff was overseen by Roswell B. Perkins, while the Foreign Policy staff was led by Henry Kissinger. In later years, DNA was headed by Oscar M. Ruebhausen. The main function of the organization was to draft position papers and research reports on issues important to Rockefeller's pursuit of the Republican presidential nomination. Source: Scope and Content Note, Nelson A. Rockefeller papers, DNA, Series G (FA342)
  - Personal, 1942-1944 (Box 45, Folder 272)
  - Personal, 1943-1944 (Box 45, Folder 273)
  - Personal, 1944-1946 (Box 45, Folder 274)
  - Personal, 1956 (Box 45, Folder 275)
  - Personal Income Material, 1970, no date (Box 45, Folder 276)
  - Population and Employment Data, 1970 (Box 46, Folder 277)
  - Press Releases, 1970 (Box 46, Folder 278)
  - Princeton University Conference on the Randall Commission Report, February 4-5, 1954, 1953-1954 (Box 46, Folder 279)
  - Proposals - Escuela Agricola Panamericana, 1958 (Box 46, Folder 280)
  - Quad-City Institute of World Affairs, November 18-20, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 281)
  - Reciprocal Trade Agreements, 1940, 1943-1945 (Box 46, Folder 282)
  - References, 1948-1952, 1956-1961 (Box 46, Folder 283)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, 1954-1963 (Box 47, Folder 284)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund - Metropolitan Research Project, 1954-1956 (Box 47, Folder 285)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund - New York Metropolitan Region Study, 1957-1958 (Box 47, Folder 286)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund - New York Metropolitan Region Study, 1959-1960 (Box 48, Folder 287)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund - Special Studies Project - Overall Panel, 1959-1960 (Box 48, Folder 288)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund - Special Studies Project - Panel Reports, 1958-1961 (Box 48, Folder 289)
  - David Rockefeller, 1952, 1954-1955, 1958-1964 (Box 48, Folder 290)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1950, 1953, 1955-1957, 1959, 1961 (Box 48, Folder 291)
  - Rockefeller - Japan- Yoshisuke Aikawa, 1957-1958 (Box 48, Folder 292)
  - John D. Rockefeller 3rd, 1953-1959, 1964 (Box 49, Folder 293)
  - Laurance S. Rockefeller, 1950, 1952-1954, 1956, 1958-1961, 1963 (Box 49, Folder 294)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1950-1956 (Box 49, Folder 295)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1957-1958 (Box 49, Folder 296)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1958-1964 (Box 50, Folder 297)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller - Articles, Speeches, etc., 1959-1963 (Box 50, Folder 298)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller - Buffalo Speech Material, June 1958, 1957-1958 (Box 50, Folder 299)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller - Farm Problem Material, 1933, 1952, 1954-1958 (Box 50, Folder 300)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller - Rochester Speech, March 1958, 1955-1958 (Box 51, Folder 301)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller - Speeches and Materials, 1952-1958 (Box 51, Folder 302)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller - "Widening Boundaries of National Interest", "Foreign Affairs", July 1951 (Box 51, Folder 303)
  - Rodman Rockefeller, 1961 (Box 51, Folder 304)
  - Winthrop Rockefeller, 1947, 1953, 1961 (Box 51, Folder 305)
  - Robert S. Schultz - Study Outline and Staff Papers, 1970 (Box 51, Folder 306)
  - SL (Shaw Livermore) - Chemical Report - Correspondence, 1950-1954, 1956 (Box 51, Folder 307)
  - SL (Shaw Livermore) - Highways and Other Construction Expenditures, 1946-1965, 1954-1955 (Box 52, Folder 308)
  - SL (Shaw Livermore) - "A Survey of Commercial Banking" - Manuscript, 1955, 1957 (Box 52, Folder 309)
  - Shift Share - Materials, 1967, 1969, no date (Box 52, Folder 310)
  - Short Term Projections - GNP - Income Accounts, 1970 (Box 52, Folder 311)
  - Society for International Development, Third Annual Conference, April 28-29, 1961 - "Relationships of Economic to Social Development", 1960-1963 (Box 52, Folder 312)
  - SONJ (Standard Oil/New Jersey) - Analysis, 1952 (Box 52, Folder 313)
  - Soviet Union, 1963 (Box 52, Folder 314)
  - Special Reports for Board Meeting, Escuela Agricola Panamericana, Inc., December 1966 (Box 52, Folder 315)
  - Special Studies Project of the Rockefeller Brothers Fund, 1956-1957, 1959-1960 (Box 52, Folder 316)
  - Speeches, 1941, 1943-1944 (Box 53, Folder 317)
  - Nicolas Spulber paper - "Soviet Economic Growth, Trade, and Aid and the Soviet Penetration into the Underdeveloped Areas", 1957 (Box 53, Folder 318)
  - Staff Memos, 1970-1971, no date (Box 53, Folder 319)
  - Standard Oil Company (New Jersey), 1952, 1954-1955 (Box 53, Folder 320)
  - State Borrowing, 1958, 1964, 1966-1969 (Box 53, Folder 321)
  - State Department - Intelligence Reports, 1955-1956 (Box 53, Folder 322)
  - Statistical Background for Economic Comeback of New York State 1958-1969, 1970, no date (Box 53, Folder 323)
  - Task Group on Balance of Payments Issue, 1959-1961 (Box 54, Folder 324)
  - Terminal Conference of the United States Trade Mission to Nigeria, July 29, 1959 (Box 54, Folder 325)
  - Testimony - House of Representatives - Subcommittee on Foreign Trade and Shipping, November 29, 1944 (Box 54, Folder 326)
  - Thailand, 1960-1964 (Box 55, Folder 327)
  - Transportation, 1961 (Box 55, Folder 328)
  - UNESCO (United Nations Educational, Scientific and Cultural Organization) Conference, Boston, October 22-26, 1961 - "Private Enterprise and the Future of Africa", Panel B-32, October 24, 1961 (Box 55, Folder 329)
  - UNESCO (United Nations Educational, Scientific and Cultural Organization) Conference, Denver, September 29-October 2, 1959 - "The Pattern of Latin American Economic Growth in the post-War Period", September 30, 1959 (Box 56, Folder 330)
  - United Fruit Company, 1960 (Box 56, Folder 331)
  - United Fruit Company - Correspondence, 1954-1956 (Box 56, Folder 332)
  - United Fruit Company - Correspondence, 1957 (Box 56, Folder 333)
  - United Fruit Company - Correspondence, 1958-1959 (Box 57, Folder 334)
  - United Fruit Company - Correspondence, 1959-1961 (Box 57, Folder 335)
  - United Fruit Company - Labor-Management Correspondence, 1958-1959 (Box 57, Folder 336)
  - United Fruit Company - Tax Renegotiation Material, 1959 (Box 57, Folder 337)
  - United Nations, 1953-1956, 1958-1962 (Box 58, Folder 338)
  - United Nations - Advisory Committee on the Work Programme on Industrialization, February 1959, 1956-1959 (Box 58, Folder 339)
  - United Nations - World Population Conference, Rome, August 31-September 10, 1954 - "The Outlook for Industrial Raw Materials Demand in 1980 and its Relation to Economic Development", Stacy May Paper, 1954-1956 (Box 59, Folder 340)
  - United States Committee for the Atlantic Congress, London, June 5-10, 1959 - "A Proposal for Applying Gatt Trading Principles to Communist-Bloc Trade with the Free World", Prepared by Stacy May, 1959-1960 (Box 59, Folder 341)
  - United States Council of the International Chamber of Commerce, Inc., 1956-1957, 1960 (Box 59, Folder 342)
  - United States Government Departments - Commerce, Labor, State, 1956, 1958-1961 (Box 59, Folder 343)
  - United States and Latin America - The Caribbean Assembly, Puerto Rico, March 1-4, 1960, 1959-1960 (Box 59, Folder 344)
  - United States Mission to the United Nations, 1953-1956, 1959 (Box 59, Folder 345)
  - Urban Affairs (including Housing), 1961 (Box 60, Folder 346)
  - U. S. S. R. Economy, 1959-1960 (Box 60, Folder 347)
  - U. S. Capital Contributions and Latin American Growth, 1955 (Box 60, Folder 348)
  - U. S. National Commission for UNESCO (United Nations Educational, Scientific and Cultural Organization), 1954-1956 (Box 60, Folder 349)
  - "U. S. vs. Russian Economic Growth", Paper presented by John M. Cassels, 2nd Annual Meeting, National Association of Business Economists, October 19, 1960 (Box 60, Folder 350)
  - Venezuela, 1957 (Box 60, Folder 351)
  - Venezuelan Food Situation - Stacy May Report, 1947-1948, 1952 (Box 60, Folder 352)
  - War Production Board Statistics, 1945 (Box 60, Folder 353)
  - Western Hemisphere Day Dinner, Avenue of the Americas Association, October 10, 1963 (Box 60, Folder 354)
  - World Affairs Council of Philadelphia - "U. S. Foreign Policy: New Perspectives in 1956", Stacy May Talk, March 6, 1956 (Box 61, Folder 355)
  - World Trade Patterns and Preferences, 1960 (Box 61, Folder 356)
  - Cape Cod, 1967-1968 (Box 61, Folder 357)
  - Cape Cod, 1967-1968 (Box 61, Folder 358)
  - Cape Cod, 1967-1968 (Box 61, Folder 359)
  - McGraw-Hill Publishing Co., Inc. - Editorials - 30th-47th, 1945-1946, no date (Box 61, Folder 360)
  - John D. Wilson, 1947 (Box 61, Folder 361)
  - IBEC (International Basic Economy Corporation), 1947 (Box 61, Folder 362)
  - Cape Cod, 1945, 1967-1968 (Box 62, Folder 363)
  - Cape Cod, 1966-1968, no date (Box 62, Folder 364)
  - Cape Cod, 1966-1968 (Box 62, Folder 365)
  - Cape Cod, 1963 (Box 63, Folder 366)
  - Michael A. Heilperin, 1945 (Box 63, Folder 367)
  - Untitled folder, 1932, no date (Box 63, Folder 368)
  - Untitled folder, 1929-1931, 1936 (Box 63, Folder 369)
  - Untitled folder, 1926, 1928-1929, no date (Box 63, Folder 370)
  - Untitled folder, 1929, 1931-1932, no date (Box 63, Folder 371)
  - Untitled folder, 1970 (Box 63, Folder 372)
  - Untitled folder, 1931-1932, no date (Box 64, Folder 373)
  - World Trade Statistics, 1963-1964 (Box 64, Folder 374)
  - Untitled folder, 1970 (Box 64, Folder 375)
  - Cape Cod, 1963, 1966-1968 (Box 64, Folder 376)
  - Financial Records, 1930-1934, 1940-1941, 1944, 1961-1964, 1967-1968, 1974 (Box 64, Folder 377)
  - Insurance Policies, 1932, 1936, 1938-1941, 1944 (Box 64, Folder 378)
  - Invitations, 1944, 1962, 1970, no date (Box 64, Folder 379)
  - Legal Documents, 1920, 1930, 1940-1941, 1967-1968 (Box 64, Folder 380)
  - Lists, 1933, 1941, 1944, 1946-1948, 1970, no date (Box 65, Folder 381)
  - Manuscripts, 1940, 1944, no date (Box 65, Folder 382)
    Includes "War Production Board Industrial Reporting Experience" by David Novick and George A. Steiner; "Transportation" prepared by J. Friedman; "Contributions of Social Science Research to Defense" and "The Role of Research in Policy Making"
  - Manuscripts, 1940, no date (Box 65, Folder 383)
    Includes "A Look Ahead"; "Notation Concerning the Artist or 'Creative Designer' for the U. S. Maritime Commission"; "Our Economic Relations with Russia: The Businessman's Stake in an Understanding with Russia"; "The Production Line of Defense"; "The Progress of the Defense Commission", Radio Speech by Stacy May, November 28, 1940; "Prospectus of the Save to Travel Plan"; and "Selling Below Cost"
  - Manuscripts, 1963 (Box 65, Folder 384)
    Includes "U. S. Foreign Trade Policy"
  - Maps, 1939, 1943, 1967, no date (Box 65, Folder 385)
  - Minutes, 1946, 1959, 1967-1968 (Box 65, Folder 386)
  - Newspaper and Magazine Clippings and Articles, 1943, 1957, 1965-1968 (Box 65, Folder 387)
  - Newspaper and Magazine Clippings and Articles, 1940, 1967-1968 (Box 65, Folder 388)
  - Newspapers, 1946, 1968 (Box 66, Folder 389)
  - Notebook - Current Positions Notebook, 1962-1963 (Box 66, Folder 390)
  - Notebook - Foreign Policy - General, What NAR Advocates, 1962-1964 (Box 66, Folder 391)
  - Notebook - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, Inc., Special Studies Project: Subpanel III - U. S. International Economic Objectives and Strategy, 1956-1957 (Box 67, Folder 392)
  - Notebook - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, Inc., Special Studies Project: Subpanel IV - U. S. Economic and Social Policy, 1956-1957 (Box 67, Folder 393)
  - Notebook - The Rockefeller Family Offices, 1959 (Box 68, Folder 394)
  - Notebook - Transportation in New York State, Summary Paper and Background Paper, 1958 (Box 68, Folder 395)
  - Notes, 1920, 1924, 1941, 1961, 1964-1968, no date (Box 68, Folder 396)
  - Notes, 1946, 1953, 1963, 1968, 1970, no date (Box 68, Folder 397)
  - Notebooks, 1967, no date (Box 68, Folder 398)
  - Papers, 1944-1945, 1956, 1958, 1967, 1971 (Box 69, Folder 399)
  - Periodicals - A-B, 1944, 1946, 1967, 1970-1971 (Box 69, Folder 400)
  - Periodicals - B, 1946, 1958, 1960, 1971 (Box 69, Folder 401)
  - Periodicals - C, 1937, 1964, 1968, 1970-1971, no date (Box 69, Folder 402)
  - Periodicals - C-I, 1934-1935, 1941, 1946, 1963, 1970-1971, no date (Box 69, Folder 403)
  - Periodicals - I-N, 1940-1941, 1946, 1968, 1971 (Box 69, Folder 404)
  - Periodicals - N-Z, 1941, 1944, 1946, 1964, 1967, 1971 (Box 70, Folder 405)
  - Photographs and Proofs, 1939, 1942, 1959, 1966, no date (Box 70, Folder 406)
  - Postcards - American Airlines, undated (Box 70, Folder 407)
  - Programs, 1940, 1967-1968, 1971 (Box 70, Folder 408)
  - Prospectuses, 1967 (Box 70, Folder 409)
  - Reports - "The Economic Development of Ecuador", Stacy May, 1949 (Box 70, Folder 410)
  - Reports - "National Product in Wartime", Simon Kuznets, undated (Box 70, Folder 411)
  - Reports - Major Issues of the Kennedy Round, Pamela Hill, 1964 (Box 70, Folder 412)
  - Reports - Record of Life Insurance Investments, Report by James J. O'Leary, 1966 (Box 71, Folder 413)
  - Reports - Report to the Directors of the American Committee on United Europe, 1959 (Box 71, Folder 414)
  - Reports - Toward a Regional Planning and Economic Development Program for Cape Cod, Planning Report No. 3, 1968 (Box 71, Folder 415)
  - Reports - Columbia Broadcasting Systems, Inc. (CBS), 1970-1971 (Box 71, Folder 416)
  - Reports - From War to Peace: Civilian Production Achievements in Transition, John D. Small, 1946 December 6 (Box 71, Folder 417)
  - Reports - Report on the Conference on African Resources, 1961 March 27-29 (Box 71, Folder 418)
  - Reports - Industrial Survey of the Resources of the Province of Newfoundland, 1950 (Box 71, Folder 419)
  - Reports - White House Conference on International Cooperation - Report of the Committee on Trade, 1965 November 28-December 1 (Box 71, Folder 420)
  - Reports - Insurance Department, Supervision of Insurance Industry, Planning - Programming - Budgetary Systems - Departmental Summary, 1967 June 21 (Box 71, Folder 421)
  - Reports - International Basic Economy Corporation, 1970 Annual Report (Box 71, Folder 422)
  - Reports - The Economic Outlook for New York State - New York State Tax Revenues, 1971-1972 (Box 71, Folder 423)
  - Reports - Report on Radio Corporation of America (RCA) International Division, 1945 October 1 (Box 72, Folder 424)
  - Reports - Preliminary Report on Public Utility Holding Companies, Preliminary Draft, 1967 July (Box 72, Folder 425)
  - Reports - Various, 1946, 1961-1962, 1967-1968, no date (Box 72, Folder 426)
  - Reprints, 1946, 1963-1964, 1967, no date (Box 72, Folder 427)
  - Resumes - Various Individuals, 1946, 1965, no date (Box 72, Folder 428)
  - Schedules, 1942, 1944, 1967-1968 (Box 72, Folder 429)
  - Studies of American Interests in the War and the Peace, Council on Foreign Relations, Inc., 1940-1941 (Box 72, Folder 430)
    General
    11 pieces
  - Studies of American Interests in the War and the Peace, Council on Foreign Relations, Inc., 1941-1944 (Box 72, Folder 431)
    7 pieces
  - Studies of American Interests in the War and the Peace, Council on Foreign Relations, Inc., 1940-1941, 1944 (Box 73, Folder 432)
    4 pieces
  - Study of Economic Possibilities for a Paper Mill at Baie d'Espoir, Newfoundland, 1951 February 15 (Box 73, Folder 433)
  - Summaries, 1957, 1963, no date (Box 73, Folder 434)
  - Tax Forms - Blank, 1941, 1964 (Box 73, Folder 435)
  - Miscellaneous, 1940, 1956 (Box 73, Folder 436)
  - Miscellaneous, 1959-1960, 1963, 1965 (Box 73, Folder 437)
  - Miscellaneous, 1944, 1946, 1948, 1951, 1967, no date (Box 73, Folder 438)
  - Miscellaneous, 1961-1962 (Box 73, Folder 439)
  - Miscellaneous, 1965, no date (Box 74, Folder 440)
  - Miscellaneous - Win with Rockefeller: Summary of Statements and Record of Nelson A. Rockefeller on Major Issues - Campaign Research Kit, 1964 (Box 74, Folder 441)
  - Miscellaneous, 1945, 1964, 1966-1967 (Box 74, Folder 442)
  - Miscellaneous, 1934, 1940-1941, 1946, 1958, 1971, no date (Box 74, Folder 443)
  - Miscellaneous, 1965, no date (Box 74, Folder 444)
  - Miscellaneous, 1970, no date (Box 74, Folder 445)
  - Miscellaneous, 1970-1971, no date (Box 74, Folder 446)
  - IBEC (International Basic Economy Corporation) - "Industrial Potentials of Ireland: An Appraisal", 1952; Oversized material (Box 75, Folder 447)
  - "Change, Challenge, Response: An Development Policy for New York State", 1964; Oversized material (Box 75, Folder 448)
  - "Cape Cod 1980: A Sector of the Massachusetts State Plan", College Hill Press, August 1963, 1963-1965, 1967-1968; Oversized material (Box 75, Folder 448A)
- Subgroup 2, 1932-1971; 2; 11.99 Cubic Feet 25 legal-sized document boxes, 1 half-legal-sized document box
  Subgroup 2 contains Stacy May's files from 1932-1971. There are a large number of U. S. government publications dating from the years during and immediately after World War II (1941-1947), when Stacy May served with the War Production Board. Also included in this subgroup is material about Escuela Agricola Americana, the National Planning Association, and several folders designated "Stacy May – Personal" (1932-1940).
  - Stacy May Personal 1932 (Box 76, Folder 449)
  - Stacy May Personal 1933 (Box 76, Folder 450-451)
  - Stacy May Personal 1934 (Box 76, Folder 452-454)
  - Stacy May Personal 1935 (Box 76, Folder 455-456)
  - Stacy May Personal 1936 (Box 77, Folder 457-458)
  - Stacy May Personal 1937 (Box 77, Folder 459-461)
  - Stacy May Personal 1938 (Box 77, Folder 462-464)
  - Stacy May Personal 1939 (Box 77, Folder 465)
  - Stacy May Personal 1940 (Box 78, Folder 466)
  - SM - Speeches, 1932, 1939 (Box 78, Folder 467)
  - Personal A-Z, 1942 (Box 78, Folder 468-470)
    Folder 468 - A-K; Folder 469 - L-Q; Folder 470 - R-Z
  - Speeches - 1940 (Box 78, Folder 471)
    "Value of Defense Contracts Awarded by Federal Reserve Districts", November 12; "Defense Construction", November 13; "The Role of Research in Policy Making", November 14; "The Progress of the Defense Commission" (Radio Speech), November 28
  - Speeches - 1941 (Box 78, Folder 472)
    "Contributions of Social Science Research to the Defense Program", April 26; Speech to the Society for the Advancement of Management, May 23; Radio Speech as part of Northwestern University's program "The Reviewing Stand", June 1; "Development of the Defense Program and Its Influence on Retailing", June 2; "Persisting Values and Changing Devices", June 8; Radio Address Re: General Status of the Defense Program, October 9; "The Production Line of Defense", October 25; "Butter, Guns, or Both", November 12; "Guns, Not Circuses", December 22
  - Speeches - 1942 (Box 78, Folder 473)
    "Economic Research in Wartime", April 24; "The Government Report Problem: Some Constructive Suggestions for Its Improvement", September 21; "Progress of War Production", October 16
  - Correspondence re Planning Study - NY, 1965 (Box 79, Folder 474)
  - NY State - Economic Materials from Departments, 1965 (Box 79, Folder 475)
  - Twentieth Century Fund: Survey on East-West Trade, 1964 (Box 79, Folder 476)
  - New York State - Worksheets and Tables, 1958 (Box 79, Folder 477)
  - New York State - 1962 Campaign (Box 79, Folder 478)
  - Unfoldered Material, 1963-1965 (Box 79, Folder 479)
  - Calendar Sheets - December 1963-December 1964 (Box 79, Folder 480)
  - Insurance Regulation, 1969 (Box 79, Folder 481)
  - Committee for a National Trade Policy - Statements, 1964 (Box 79, Folder 482)
  - International Cooperation Year - Trade Policy, 1964-1965, 1968 (Box 80, Folder 483)
  - Minutes of March 23 Meeting: Topic - Suggestions for Cabinet Committee, 1965 (Box 80, Folder 484)
  - Escuela Agricola Panamericana, 1964-1965 (Box 80, Folder 485)
  - Thailand Project, 1952, 1957, 1959-1963, 1965 (Box 80, Folder 486-489, Box 81, Folder 490-495)
  - Source Book of Historical Statistics, 1946 (Box 82, Folder 496)
  - "War Progress" - War Production Board, Numbers 43, 69-262, 1941-1945 (Box 82, Folder 497-500, Box 83, Folder 501-507, Box 84, Folder 508-512)
    Folder 497 - Numbers 43, 69-76, 1941 June, 1942 January-February; Folder 498 - Numbers 77-84, 1942 March-April; Folder 499 - Numbers 85-93, 1942 May-June; Folder 500 - Numbers 94-106, 1942 July-September; Folder 501 - Numbers 107-119, 1942 October-December; Folder 502 - Numbers 120-132, 1943 January-March; Folder 503 - Numbers 133-145, 1943 April-June; Folder 504 - Numbers 146-158, 1943 July-September; Folder 505 - Numbers 159-171, 1943 October-December; Folder 506 - Numbers 172-184, 1944 January-March; Folder 507 - Numbers 185-197, 1944 April-June; Folder 508 - Numbers 198-211, 1944 July-September; Folder 509 - Numbers 212-224, 1944 October-December; Folder 510 - Numbers 225-237, 1945 January-March; Folder 511 - Numbers 238-250, 1945 April-June; Folder 512 - Numbers 251-262, 1945 July-October
  - "Defense Progress", Number 50, Part A, Annual Review, 1941 August (Box 84, Folder 513)
  - "The War Production Programs 1943-1944"; "Accuracy of Material Supply Estimates"; "Gross National Product 1939-1944" - Document Numbers 1-10, 12-13 - War Production Board, 1943 July-November (Box 84, Folder 514)
  - "War Production and Civilian Output After Victory in Europe", Document Numbers 14, 17-20 - War Production Board, 1944 January-September (Box 85, Folder 515)
  - "Regional and Industry Impacts of War Production", Document Numbers 15-16 - War Production Board, 1944 February (Box 85, Folder 516)
  - "World Munitions Production 1938-1944", Document Number 21 - War Production Board, 1944 July (Box 85, Folder 517)
  - "The War Production Program of 1945 and Its Impact", Document Numbers 24, 24A-D, 24F - War Production Board, 1945 March (Box 85, Folder 518)
  - "The World Production of Munitions at the End of the War in Europe", Document Number 25 - War Production Board, 1945 June (Box 85, Folder 519)
  - "American Industry in War and Transition, 1940-1950", Document Number 27- War Production Board, 1945 July (Box 85, Folder 520)
  - "The Effects of Atomic Bombs on Hiroshima and Nagasaki" - The United States Strategic Bombing Survey, 1946 June (Box 85, Folder 521)
  - "Summary Report (Pacific War)" - United States Strategic Bombing Survey, 1946 July (Box 85, Folder 522)
  - "Statistics of War Contract Terminations and Settlements January-June 1946" - Office of Contract Settlement, 1946 August (Box 85, Folder 523)
  - "From War to Peace: Civilian Production Achievements in Transition" - Civilian Production Administration, 1946 December (Box 85, Folder 524)